#### e: david.dilanchian@pm.me

## **David Dilanchian**

w: https://davidldilanchian.info

m: (514) 515-2845

#### Personal Profile

Experienced Contractor with a demonstrated history of working in the computer and network security industry. Skilled in Negotiation, Analytical Skills, Microsoft Office, Fintech, OS Development, Product Knowledge, and Management. Strong professional & entrepreneurship studied at Université de Montréal.

### Work Experience

## Co-Founder at HayFinTech

January 2017 - Present

• Research, design, develop, and test blockchain technologies • Maintain and extend current client- and server-side applications responsible for integration and business logic • Be involved in the global blockchain community—work on implementing and integrating the latest improvement proposals

## Web Analyst at Show Viral

December 2015 - Present

 Produce reports for the Management team
Plan, develop and manage web and mobile campaign and channel tracking
Collaborate with sales and marketing teams

## Manager & Owner at Cafe Babylonia

April 2013 - December 2015

My Coffee Shop • Manage day-to-day operations of the coffee shop • Hire & Train Employees • Nurture friendly relationships with customers to increase loyalty

## Sales Representative at Action 500 Paintball & Karting

March 2012 - April 2013

Promote & sell products and services while exceeding sales forecasts Establish, develop and maintain positive business and customer relationships Analyze the territory/market's potential, track sales and status reports

# Sales Representative at SAIL Outdoor Equipment Store

March 2011 - April 2012

Educate customers on how products or services can benefit them financially & professionally Maintaining positive business relationships to ensure future sales Supply management with reports on customer needs, problems, interests, competitive activities, and potential for new products

## Grill Master at Harvey's

April 2007 - December 2011

Trained and managed a team of 3 prep-cooks and achieved significant improvements in their productivity. Monitoring consistently the food quality and service quality of orders being served. Successfully handled opening and closing of establishment.

## **Projects**

#### **SCAMA**

https://github.com/david-dilan/SCAMA

Teaching Senior Citizens how to start and use Computers/Social Media/Internet - Windows 10 / iOS / Android - Gmail / YouTube / Google

#### Scouts Leader at Homenetmen Montreal

https://www.homenetmenmontreal.com

Scout Leaders are primarily responsible for organizing the activities of the group, and training the youth members through the Scout program. - Leadership - Liaison with Parents/Districts

## Laval Electoral Campaign 2017

https://www.laval.ca/

Electoral Campaign Volunteer during the 2017 Laval municipal election - Market the candidate - Participated in door-to-door canvassing events

## Key Skills

Programming Microsoft Office: Word / Languages: English -C2

Languages: Python / C++ Excel / PowerPoint / (Proficient) French -C2

/ nodeJS / Typscript Access / Publisher / (Proficient) Armenian -

HTML5 / Bootstrap 4 / MyAnalytics / Visio / B1(Intermediate)

Angular 2 SharePoint

#### Education

## Vanier College

**DEC** in Social Science

September 2009 - May 2012

#### Saint-Maxime

**DES Concentrations Science** 

September 2006 - June 2009